<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Classes on Tyler H. McCormick</title>
    <link>https://thmccormick.github.io/class/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Classes on Tyler H. McCormick</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="https://thmccormick.github.io/class/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>(Preliminary) Course schedule</title>
      <link>https://thmccormick.github.io/class/567_sp19_schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thmccormick.github.io/class/567_sp19_schedule/</guid>
      <description>Stat/CSSS 566 Spring 2019, University of Washington Main page
Textbooks: Kolaczyk, Eric D. 2009. Statistical Analysis of Network Data (SAND). and Kolaczyk, Eric D. and Csárdi, G. 2014. Statistical Analysis of Network Data (SANDr). Both are available as pdf from the UW Library website.
Reading: Readings come from several disciplines and, as such, assume different levels of background knowledge. You&amp;rsquo;re encouraged to read as comprehensively as possible with the understanding that readings might be assuming familiarity with topics that are new to you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prospective students</title>
      <link>https://thmccormick.github.io/class/students/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thmccormick.github.io/class/students/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m eager to work with student and postdoctoral collaborators! Thanks for your interest! If you don&amp;rsquo;t see what you&amp;rsquo;re looking for here please get in touch. Undergraduate, Masters, and visiting students The first step in the process is to take a look around my website to see the kind of work I do and see what you find interesting. Once you&amp;rsquo;ve done that, please fill out this form to get in touch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Statistical analysis of social network data</title>
      <link>https://thmccormick.github.io/class/567_sp19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thmccormick.github.io/class/567_sp19/</guid>
      <description>Tentative syllabus, subject to change (Updated 17-Feb-2019) Stat/CSSS 566 Spring 2019, University of Washington Course schedule
Logistics Instructor: Tyler McCormick; Email: tylermc@uw.edu; Office Hours: TBD
TA: TBD Course meetings: T/Th 11:30-12:50pm (Guggenheim 218) &amp;amp; F 1:30-2:20 (Savery 264) Overview &amp;amp; objectives This course is a practical, hands-on introduction to design and analysis of social network data, set against a backdrop of theory from sociology, economics, and other disciplines.
Course components &amp;amp; grading    Component % Grade     Approx 5 HWs 40   In-class presentation 15   Final project &amp;amp; poster 45    In-class presentation: In weeks 3-9, Tuesday lectures will present statistical methods and Thursday lectures will be student presentations of social science papers that use the method.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>